diyweddingsmag.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy Policy -

**PRIVACY POLICY**

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of the website visitors and Service users; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information:

**(1) What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of our Services (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views);

(b) information relating to any purchases of our Services via the website, in an application, via the Apple App Store or otherwise (including your name, address, email address, birth date and other demographics provided by you, as well as payment details, details of the Publications you have purchased, analytics relating to your viewing of the Publications, and any information contained in any messages provided by you);

(c) the personal information identified in Sections 3 and 4 below; and

(d) any other personal information that you provide to us.

**(2) Using your personal data**

Personal data submitted on the website or through an application will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website or an application. We may use your personal information to:

(a) administer the website or any applications;

(b) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website and applications;

(c) enable your use of the Services and supply the Services to you;

(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;

(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(h) send to you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post, or email or other technology (to the extent permitted by law–you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);

(i) provide various third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

(j) provide the information described in Part E.(1) above to carefully selected partners, providers, affiliates and other third parties, including, but not limited to, publishers who provide works for download, providers of goods and services, and others to whom such information may have commercial value, none of whom will be granted rights to utilize such information to any greater extent than we are entitled to utilize such information; and

(k) deal with inquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the Website and/or the Services.

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website or through our application, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us. All our financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider. We will share information with our payment services provider only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via or in relation to our Services.

**(3) Cookies**

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser. We use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to keep track of you while you navigate the website. We will use the persistent cookies to enable the website to recognize you when you visit. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

We use Google Analytics and other analytical tools to analyze the use of this website and certain applications. These analytical tools generate statistical and other information about website or application use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to the website or an application is used to create reports about the use of the website or applications. Google will store this information obtained through Google Analytics. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, while some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

**(4) Application/Publication monitoring**

We may from time to time automatically collect information about your use of the Application and the Publications. This information includes the number of times the Application is launched, details of the Publications and Publication pages that you view, the time when you view them, your geographical location when you view them, and information about your device, system and software. We will use this information to provide you with the Services (including upgrades and bug fixes). We will use this information, in anonymised form, for the purpose of improving the Services and otherwise as provided above. We will also share this information with the owners of Publications, but, except as may be provided above, only in anonymised form. If you would prefer we not collect and use your information in this manner, you should opt-out of Application/Publication monitoring using the Application.

**(5) Disclosures**

We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy. In addition, we may disclose information about you:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**(6) International data transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the United States of America. In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world. You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

**(7) Security of your personal data**

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted using SSL technology. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.

**(8) Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on the website or otherwise through the Services. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

**(9) Your rights**

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee. You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time.

**(10) Third party websites**

The website contains, and applications may contain, links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

**(11) Updating information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

**(12) Minors**

It is our intention to comply in all respects with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”). To that end, purchasing Services is strictly limited to those who are not minors. Therefore, it is not anticipated that we will collect data relating to minors, as defined in COPPA. However, in the event that it comes to our attention that we have collected any data from or relating to a minor in any form that is not anonymised, we will promptly destroy that data, and will not distribute it to others, or keep copies thereof (other than, at our option, in a “deleted or destroyed information” file, to be used solely to evidence the destruction and non-use of that information).

### Contacting Us

We can be reached by E-mail at: [info@diyweddingsmag.com](mail:info@diyweddingsmag.com)
